Inventory of the G. Walter Mapp Papers 1895-1935
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- Correspondence of G. Walter Mapp, 1895-1935. (Box 1-8)
  - General Correspondence, 1895-1935. (Box 1-7)
    - General Correspondence: A-Ca, 1895-1935., Note: "Duplicate correspondence" refers to unsigned copies of letters by Mapp. "Original correspondence" refers to signed letters written to Mapp. (Box-folder 1:1-265)
      - Correspondence from B. T. Bowen, Broadwater, Virginia, [1911]., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:157)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Edward Bowes, New York, New York, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:158)
      - Correspondence from Rev. W. Russell Bowie, Richmond, Virginia, 1922., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:159)
      - Correspondence from E. Bradbury, American Institute of Architects, 1920., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:160)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with the Rev. J. J. Bradford, Norfolk, Virginia, 1918., 4 items. (Box-folder 1:161)
      - Correspondence with Robert L. Bradford, Jr., 1933., 4 items. (Box-folder 1:162)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Roy B. Bradley, Richmond, Virginia, 1926., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:163)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with W. L. Bragg, Richmond, Virginia, 1928-1929., 3 items. (Box-folder 1:164)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with James G. Bratten, Princess Anne, Virginia, 1914., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:165)
      - Correspondence from J. N. Brenaman, Secretary of Virginia State Democratic Committee, 1911, 1918., 4 items. (Box-folder 1:166)
      - Correspondence from R. S. Brent, Heatheville, Virginia, 1918., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:167)
      - Correspondence from R. A. Brice, Philadelphia, 1909., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:168)
      - Correspondence from H. L. Bridges, Williamsburg, Virginia, 1 item. (Box-folder 1:169)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with J. Fulmer Bright, Richmond, Virginia, 1928., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:170)
      - Correspondence from Asie M. Brimer, Girdletree, Virginia, 1918., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:171)
      - Correspondence with the Bristol Herald-Courier, Bristol, Virginia, 1925., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:172)
      - Correspondence from Herwood Bristow, Onancock, Virginia, 1922., 4 items. (Box-folder 1:173)
      - Correspondence from M. E. Bristow, Cape Charles, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:174)
      - Correspondence from M. E. Brittingham, Wachapreague, Virginia, 1910., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:175A)
      - Correspondence to O. J. Brittingham, Wythe, Virginia, 1914., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:175B)
      - Correspondence from the Britts Mercantile Agency, 1925., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:176)
      - Correspondence from Andrew Broaddus, Sparta, Virginia, 1918., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:177)
      - Duplicate correspondence to W. T. Broaddus, Hutton, Virginia, 1920., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:178)
      - Correspondence from Lloyd N. Broadwater, Washington, D.C., 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:179)
      - Telegram from J. A. Brockenbrough, Warsaw, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:180)
      - Duplicate correspondence to S. S. Brooks, Appalachia, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:181)
      - Duplicate correspondence to J. W. Broughton, Hallwood, Virginia, 1928., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:182)
      - Correspondence from E. D. Brown, Exmore, Virginia, 1911., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:183)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with G. W. Brown, Williamsburg, Virginia, 1918., 3 items. (Box-folder 1:184)
      - Correspondence from H. S. Brown, New York, 1924., 4 items. (Box-folder 1:185)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Jack Brown, Hampton, Virginia, 1914., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:186)
      - Duplicate correspondence to J. St. Clair Brown, Salem, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:187)
      - Correspondence from Mary Brown, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:188)
      - Duplicate correspondence to A. P. Brush, Wauchula, Florida, 1932, 1935., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:189)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with John Stewart Bryan of the Richmond News Leader, 1929-1933., 4 items. (Box-folder 1:190)
      - Correspondence from Arthur H. Bryant, Alexandria, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:191)
      - Correspondence from William H. Bryant, Richmond, Virginia, 1926., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:192)
      - Correspondence from Anne Buchanan, Richmond, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:193)
      - Correspondence from Lt. Gov. B. F. Buchanan, Richmond, Virginia, 1920., 7 items. (Box-folder 1:194)
      - Correspondence from G. L. Buchanan, of Richmond YMCA, n.d., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:195)
      - Correspondence from H. G. Buchanan, Richmond, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:196)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with J. P. Buchanan, Marian, Virginia, 1924., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:197)
      - Box-Folder 1:198 currently does not exist in this collection. (Box-folder Box-Folder 148 currently does not exist in this collection.)
      - Telegram from J. W. Buchanan and Sons, Norfolk, Virginia, 1912., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:199)
      - Correspondence from Estelee W. Bundick, n.d., 3 items. (Box-folder 1:200)
      - Correspondence from Norman Bundick, Bloxom, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:201)
      - Correspondence from G. T. Bunn, Williamsburg, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:202)
      - Correspondence from A. L. Bunting, Bloxom, Virginia, 1910., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:203)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with William C. Bunting, Chincoteague, Virginia., 3 items. (Box-folder 1:204A)
      - Correspondence from Charles Bunting, Quinby, Virginia., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:204B)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with I. J. Burbage, Cape Charles, Virginia, 1911-1922., 5 items. (Box-folder 1:205)
      - Telegram from C. E. Burch, Chincoteague, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:206)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Georgiana Burdick, Denver, Colorado, 1932-1933., 3 items. (Box-folder 1:207)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence to the Bureau of Markets, Pocomoke City, Maryland, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:208)
      - Correspondence from R. L. Burke, Appomattox, Virginia, 1923., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:209)
      - Correspondence from M. C. Burke, St. Stephens, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:210)
      - Correspondence from Rev. William Burleigh, College Park, Maryland, 1926., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:211)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Rev. R. W. Burnett, Brandy Station, Virginia, 1928., 4 items. (Box-folder 1:212)
      - Correspondence from F. A. M. Burroughs, Princess Anne, Virginia, 1911, 1912., 3 items. (Box-folder 1:213)
      - Correspondence from W.C. Burroughs, Assawamon, Virginia, 1911., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:214)
      - Correspondence from [G.T. Burson?], Keller, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:215)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with William Stanley Burt, Commonwealth's Attorney for Surry County, 1928., 3 items. (Box-folder 1:216)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Eloise Burton, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1911, 1932., 3 items. (Box-folder 1:217)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Vernon S. Burton, Onley, Virginia, 1931-1932., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:218)
      - Correspondence from W. A. Burton, Onley, Virginia, 1906., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:219)
      - Duplicate correspondence to William M. Burwell, Chincoteague, Virginia, 1912., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:220)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Howard M. Busick, Baltimore, Maryland, 1935., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:221)
      - Correspondence from D. G. C. Butts, Franktown, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:222)
      - Correspondence from Henry R. [Bylen?], Norfolk, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:223)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Austin Byrd, Keller, Virginia, 1929, 1934., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:224)
      - Correspondence pertaining to Carrie E. Byrd, Wachapreague, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:225)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Colmore E. Byrd, Pocornoke City, Maryland, 1909-1931., 6 items. (Box-folder 1:226)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with G. F. Byrd, Sanford, Virginia, 1911., 6 items. (Box-folder 1:227)
      - Correspondence with Harry Flood Byrd, Governor and Senator of Virginia, 1920-1935., 37 items. (Box-folder 1:228-230)
        - Duplicate and original correspondence with Harry Flood Byrd, 1920-1922., 14 items. (Box-folder 1:228)
        - Duplicate and original correspondence with Harry Flood Byrd, 1923-1929., 15 items. (Box-folder 1:229)
        - Correspondence with Harry Flood Byrd, 1933-1935., 8 items. (Box-folder 1:230)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Lt. John Byrd, New London, Connecticut, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:231)
      - Correspondence from Lee Byrd, Mears, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:232)
      - Correspondence from M. J. Byrd, Mears, Virginia, 1912., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:233)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with M. S. Byrd, Charlottesville, Virginia, 1931., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:234)
      - Correspondence from Milton Byrd, Onley, Virginia, 1925., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:235)
      - Correspondence from Ortho W. Byrd, Temperanceville, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:236)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with R. E. Byrd, Richmond, Virginia, 1918., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:237)
      - Correspondence with Staton F. Byrd, Poulson, Virginia, 1918-1927., 19 items. (Box-folder 1:238-240)
        - Duplicate and original correspondence with Staton F. Byrd, Poulson, Virginia, 1918-1923., 4 items. (Box-folder 1:238)
        - Correspondence with Staton F. Byrd, 1924., 10 items. (Box-folder 1:239)
        - Correspondence with Staton F. Byrd, 1927., 5 items. (Box-folder 1:240)
      - Correspondence from P. H. Callahan, Louisville, Kentucky, 1927., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:241)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Mr. [?] Callahan, Painter, Virginia, 1935., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:242)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Camp Manufacturing Company, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:243)
      - Correspondence from Thomas M. Campbell, Camden, South Carolina, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:244)
      - Correspondence with the Rev. James Cannon, an important figure in the Prohibition movement, 1911-1940, n.d., 104 items. (Box-folder 1:245-254)
        - Correspondence with the Rev. James Cannon, 1911., 5 items. (Box-folder 1:245)
        - Correspondence with Rev. James Cannon, July-August 1914., 6 items. (Box-folder 1:246)
        - Correspondence with Rev. James Cannon, September 1914., 12 items. (Box-folder 1:247)
        - Correspondence with Rev. James Cannon, October-November 1914., 10 items. (Box-folder 1:248)
        - Correspondence with Rev. James Cannon, December 1914., 11 items. (Box-folder 1:249)
        - Correspondence with Rev. James Cannon, 1915-1916., 18 items. (Box-folder 1:250)
        - Correspondence with Rev. James Cannon, 1917-1918., 20 items. (Box-folder 1:251)
        - Correspondence with Rev. James Cannon, 1919-1928., 10 items. (Box-folder 1:252)
        - Correspondence with Rev. James Cannon, 1934-1940., 9 items. (Box-folder 1:253)
        - Correspondence with Rev. James Cannon, n.d., 3 items. (Box-folder 1:254)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Hudson Carey, Richmond, Virginia, 1920., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:255)
      - Duplicate correspondence to C. C. Carlin, Washington, D.C., 1929., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:256)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Harry Carmine, Wattsville, Virginia., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:257)
      - Correspondence from W. Leigh Carneal, Richmond, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:258)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Wm. C. Carson, Riverton, Virginia, 1934., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:259)
      - Correspondence from Wm. E. Carson, Riverton, Virginia, 1912., 5 items. (Box-folder 1:260)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with C. S. Carter, Bristol, Virginia, 1922, 1924., 2 items. (Box-folder 1:261)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Mrs. Hickman Carter, Danville, Kentucky, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:262)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with John W. Carter, Danville, Virginia, 1925-1928., 10 items. (Box-folder 1:263)
      - Correspondence from T. A. Cary, Richmond, Virginia, 1906., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:264)
      - Correspondence from J. W. Castle, Cape Charles, Virginia, 1912., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:265)
    - General Correspondence: Ce-Fl, 1895-1935., Note: "Duplicate correspondence" refers to unsigned copies of letters by Mapp. "Original correspondence" refers to signed letters written to Mapp. (Box-folder 2:1-264)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with George M. Cease, Richmond, Virginia, 1922-1934., 6 items. (Box-folder 2:1)
      - Open letter to the Citizens of Accomac County, 1911., 2 items. (Box-folder 2:2)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with John W. Chalkley, Big Stone Gap, Virginia, 1927., 4 items. (Box-folder 2:3)
      - Correspondence from A. S. Chandler, Parkeley, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:4)
      - Correspondence from C. F. Chandler, Bloxom, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:5)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with J. A. C. Chandler, President of the College of William and Mary, 1920-1926., 16 items. (Box-folder 2:6)
      - Duplicate correspondence to J. W. Chandler, Exmore, Virginia, 1932, 1935., 2 items. (Box-folder 2:7)
      - Correspondence from Mrs. White Chandler, Parksley, Virginia, 1934., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:8)
      - Duplicate correspondence to T. W. Chapman, Smithfield, Virginia., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:9)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Roy Charles, Newport News, Virginia., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:10)
      - Correspondence from Mrs. Della Charnock, Tangier, Virginia, 1931., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:11)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Walter L. Charnock, Richmond, Virginia, 1922, 1927., 2 items. (Box-folder 2:12)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Kellam Chase, Poulson, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:13)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Lee Chase, Richmond, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:14)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Chase and Sanborn Radio Hour, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:15)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Chatham Manufacturing Company, Elkin, North Carolina, 1932-1933., 2 items. (Box-folder 2:16)
      - Duplicate correspondence to the Chemical Foundation, New York, 1934., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:17)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Fred R. Chenault, Richmond and Danville, Virginia, 1922, 1933-1934., 4 items. (Box-folder 2:18)
      - Correspondence from Ernest H. Cherrington, the Anti-Saloon League of America, 1920, 1924., 2 items. (Box-folder 2:19)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Viola Cherrix, Chincoteague, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:20)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with John W. Cherry, Norfolk, Virginia, 1918., 3 items. (Box-folder 2:21)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Chesapeake and Potomac Telephone Company, 1920., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:22)
      - Correspondence to John S. Chesser, Hallwood, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:23)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Evan R. Chesterman, Richmond, Virginia, 1922., 3 items. (Box-folder 2:24)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Cassius M. Chichester, Richmond, Virginia, 1935., 3 items. (Box-folder 2:25)
      - Correspondence from Godfrey Child, Pocomoke City, Maryland, 1931., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:26)
      - Duplicate correspondence to The Children's Home Society, Richmond, Virginia, 1932-1933., 2 items. (Box-folder 2:27)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Joseph W. Chinn, Commissioner of Fisheries, 1930., 4 items. (Box-folder 2:28)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Mr. Cholley, Williamsburg, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:29)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Frank P. Clark, Baltimore, Maryland, 1898-1900., 31 items. (Box-folder 2:30)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with John R. Clark, Stuart, Virginia, 1922, 1929., 5 items. (Box-folder 2:31)
      - Correspondence from J. B. Clark, Norge, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:32)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Adele Clarke, President of the Virginia League of Women Voters, 1920-1932., 14 items. (Box-folder 2:33)
      - Correspondence from E. H. Clawes, Richmond, Virginia, 1925., 2 items. (Box-folder 2:34)
      - Duplicate correspondence to J. D. Clay, Coeburg, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:35)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with A. H. Clement, Appomattox, Virginia, 1926., 4 items. (Box-folder 2:36)
      - Correspondence form S. T. Clover, Richmond, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:37)
      - Correspondence from E. Chishoim Cobb, Penola, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:38)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Henry W. Cobb, Wachapreague, Virginia, 1932., 2 items. (Box-folder 2:39)
      - Correspondence from W. J. Cobb, Onancock, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:40)
      - Duplicate correspondence to James Cogar, Williamsburg, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:41)
      - Correspondence from Philip V. Cogbill, Chesterfield, Virginia, 1912., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:42)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Cohnand Bock, Princess Anne, Maryland, 1935., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:43)
      - Duplicate correspondence from Newton J. Cole, Dwight, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:44)
      - Duplicate correspondence to George P. Coleburn, Williamsburg, Virginia, 1929-1931., 3 items. (Box-folder 2:45)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with C. R. Coleman, Snell, Virginia, 1924., 3 items. (Box-folder 2:46)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with George P. Coleman, Williamsburg, Virginia, 1928-1932., 6 items. (Box-folder 2:47)
      - Correspondence from Mary Haldane Coleman, Richmond, Virginia, n.d., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:48)
      - Correspondence from William L. Coleman, Charlottesville, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:49)
      - Duplicate correspondence to John W. Coles, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, n.d., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:50)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Mr. Coliveta, Richmond, Virginia, 1935., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:51)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Collector of Customs, Norfolk, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:52)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Harry N. Collins, Franklin City, Virginia, 1934., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:53)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence from Oliver D. Collins, Snow Hill, Maryland, 1910-1911., 2 items. (Box-folder 2:54)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Barron G. Colloer, Richmond, Virginia, 1918., 2 items. (Box-folder 2:55)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Howard T. Colvin, Richmond, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:56)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with E. R. Combs, Bristol, Virginia, 1924., 2 items. (Box-folder 2:57)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Commandant of the U.S. Coast Guard Service, Washington, D.C., 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:58)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Commercial Service Corporation, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:59)
      - Duplicate correspondence to T. C. Commins, Rumford, Virginia, 1923., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:60)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Commissioner of Labor, Richmond, Virginia., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:61)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Henry W. Conant, Chincoteague, Virginia, 1920, 1932., 3 items. (Box-folder 2:62)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Leroy E. Conant, Chincoteague, Virginia, 1932-1933., 4 items. (Box-folder 2:63)
      - Correspondence from W. N. Conant, Chincoteague, Virginia, 1911., 4 items. (Box-folder 2:64)
      - Duplicate correspondence to the Confederate Home for Women, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:65)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Helen G. Conquest, Greta, Virginia, 1932-1933., 2 items. (Box-folder 2:66)
      - Correspondence with George N. Conrad, Dry State Senator from Harrisonburg, Virginia, 1926-1933., 36 items. (Box-folder 2:67-69)
        - Duplicate and original correspondence with George N. Conrad, 1926-1927., 15 items. (Box-folder 2:67)
        - Duplicate and original correspondence with George N. Conrad, 1928-1929., 15 items. (Box-folder 2:68)
        - Duplicate and original correspondence with George N. Conrad, 1930-1933., 6 items. (Box-folder 2:69)
      - Correspondence from Robert B. Cooke, Norfolk, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:70)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with W. S. Copeland, Newport News, Virginia, 1923., 5 items. (Box-folder 2:71)
      - Duplicate correspondence to R. T. Corbell, Richmond, Virginia, 1927., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:72)
      - Correspondence from C. F. Corbin, Sanford, Virginia, n.d., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:73)
      - Duplicate correspondence to E. J. Corbin, Quinby, Virginia., 2 items. (Box-folder 2:74)
      - Correspondence from Leland S. Corbin, Quinby, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:75)
      - Correspondence from Mary S. Corbin, [Washington, D.C.], 1910-1911., 2 items. (Box-folder 2:76)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with R. J. Corbin, Hallwood, Virginia, 1925., 2 items. (Box-folder 2:77)
      - Correspondence from James H. Corbitt, Suffolk, Virginia, 1928., 3 items. (Box-folder 2:78)
      - Correspondence from S. J. Costen, Cheapside, Virginia, 1912., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:79)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with G. E. Coulbourn, Nassawadox and Cape Charles, Virginia, 1911, 1922, 1929., 7 items. (Box-folder 2:80)
      - Correspondence from Martha E. Coulling, Farmville, Virginia, 1920., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:81)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Kathryn P. Couper, Norfolk, Virginia, 1922, 1928., 4 items. (Box-folder 2:82)
      - Correspondence from G. W. Covington, New Church, Virginia, 1910., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:83)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with E. P. Cox, Richmond, Virginia, 1929., 3 items. (Box-folder 2:84)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with S. C. Cox, Galax, Virginia, 1926., 2 items. (Box-folder 2:85)
      - Correspondence from W. A. Cox, Norfolk, Virginia, 1935., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:86)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with A. P. Craddock, Lynchburg, Virginia, 1926., 2 items. (Box-folder 2:87)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Wilbur F. Crafts, Washington, D.C., 1922., 3 items. (Box-folder 2:88)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with William Crenshaw, 1925., 2 items. (Box-folder 2:89)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Mr. Cridlin, Richmond, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:90)
      - Correspondence from J. M. Crockett, Pocomoke City, Maryland, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:91)
      - Duplicate correspondence to William H. Crockett, Accomac, Virginia, 1932, 1935., 2 items. (Box-folder 2:92)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Zella Mapp Crockett, Pocomoke City, Maryland, 1931., 2 items. (Box-folder 2:93)
      - Duplicate correspondence to A. C. Cromwell, Sheriff of Norfolk County, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:94A)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Mrs. L. Croonenburgh, Lynnhaven, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:94B)
      - Correspondence from Floridus S. Crosby, Staunton, Virginia, 1921., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:95)
      - Duplicate correspondence to John R. Crowson, Justisville, Virginia, 1928., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:96)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Walker R. Crump, Richmond, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 2:97)